<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Robin Chandra</title>
    <link>https://robinchandra.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Robin Chandra</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2021 17:00:50 +0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://robinchandra.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>First Job: Vitol</title>
      <link>https://robinchandra.github.io/posts/work_experiences/vitol_app/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2021 17:00:50 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://robinchandra.github.io/posts/work_experiences/vitol_app/</guid>
      <description>Today, I signed my first full-time employment contract offer. It was quite an emotional moment for me, whose path to get a decent job was rough and full of challenges but more on that in the upcoming post. For now, I will discuss more regarding my job application journey with Vitol. Vitol, a Dutch energy and commodity trading company is the largest independent energy trader in the world.
An Initiative I noticed the job opening a few weeks back, around the end of June, and immediately thought that this might be it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Internship with Chevron</title>
      <link>https://robinchandra.github.io/posts/work_experiences/chevron/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2020 06:20:50 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://robinchandra.github.io/posts/work_experiences/chevron/</guid>
      <description>This is an account of my internship with Chevron. It was part of my course requirement. At first, I saw the opening on NUS Talent Connect, which is an online job listing platform aimed to help NUS students and alumni alike to find jobs, internships, etc. The application process is typical, but there is an interesting story to share during the interview.
Hot and Humid On the day of the interview, I was not prepared for the hot and humid weather of Singapore.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to RC&#39;s Archive</title>
      <link>https://robinchandra.github.io/posts/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2020 01:27:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://robinchandra.github.io/posts/welcome/</guid>
      <description>This website is created to be used as my autobiography, as a platform to share my experiences and also to practice my web developing skill. I came across this idea in June 2020, just as I finished my internship and have a bit of free time. Therefore, there might still be some bugs here and there. Don’t hesitate to give your feedback, ask questions, or even share your own experience.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>